Your symptoms...
I think we need to run some tests on your heart.
Based on your EKG and lab results as well as the echocardiogram,
you've been diagnosed with dilated cardiomyopathy.
Dilated cardiomyopathy?
What's that?
It's when the heart gets enlarged and can't pump blood effectively.
If you don't get admitted and start treatment right away,
your heart could stop as soon as tonight.
Wait...
What did you just say?
I'm...
going to die?
We can manage the symptoms, but a full recovery is unlikely.
Your heart function is so poor that it could stop at any time,
and it wouldn't be surprising if you died suddenly.
You're essentially a walking time bomb.
The only real treatment...
is a heart transplant.
A heart...
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
transplant?
Yes. Ultimately, you will need a heart transplant.
Please help him with the admission paperwork.
(Team Leader's Office)
I guess the meeting at HQ is running late.
I don't remember it ever taking this long.
(Seongshin General Hospital)
(Lee Ji Hyuk)
(Inpatient Admission Information)
- Here you go. - Thank you.
And now, please head to the MRI room.
Hold on a second.
Sure.
I'm so worried, I can't get any work done.
I should just go return this to him.
Yes, I understand.
Mr. Lee is flying to Tokyo now. It's a three-day trip.
- So suddenly? - What for?
I'm sure it's for company business.
I get that, but what kind of company business?
So abruptly?
He didn't say a word about it at lunch.
I don't think you need to know the CEO's schedule, Ms. Ji.
Excuse me?
Hey, something must have come up at HQ.
Right.
I'm just an employee, after all.
It's not Cheol Min's place to say.
I'm sure he'll contact you.
(Jamun Medical Devices)
(My eldest son)
Son. What's going on?
Mom.
I'm at the airport right now. You see...
I have to make a quick trip to Tokyo for work.
So suddenly?
Is there a problem at the company?
No, it's just...
There are some materials I have to check on urgently.
It's for three days.
Three days?
Then what about your clothes and everything?
I can buy them in Japan. You can get anything there.
Right.
So, Mom, have you ever been to Japan?
Before I got married, with my friends...
We went to Kyoto for three days.
We loved it so much, we said we'd go to Tokyo next time,
but then I got married and had you kids one after another.
And Grandfather got sick, right?
Right.
We were so busy with life, there was never a chance.
Hello?
Ji Hyuk.
Mom.
What were you doing?
What do you think? I was working.
Ji Hyuk, I made three sales today!
You did? No wonder you sound so cheerful.
That's part of it, but it's also because you called...
and asked me about Japan.
Just because I...
asked if you've ever been to Japan?
That's enough to make you happy?
Of course. You know I love your attention.
Listen to me, chattering away while you're at the airport.
Gosh, how silly of me.
Ji Hyuk, I'll let you go.
Have a safe trip and take care of business.
Okay, Mom.
I'll have a safe trip.
(Shoealls)
(CEO Park Jin Seok)
(Ji Eun Oh: Personal Information)
(Family Relation Certificate)
(Han Yu Ra, Deceased)
(October 1999)
Why are you crying like she just died today?
It's been so many years.
I just registered her death today.
Today?
Why would you file it today?
Now that I'm marrying you,
I knew I couldn't hold on to her any longer.
She died a month after her dad passed away,
but I just couldn't accept that she was gone.
You should have asked me to go with you.
How could you do that all alone and just sit here crying?
I've been telling you to just move in with me.
You already quit your job,
so why are you still living in this cramped place?
But we're not married yet. That wouldn't be right.
Your parents live there, too.
And we have to consider Shoe Joy's reputation as well.
It's absolutely out of the question.
Wow, Ko Seong Hui, you're really something else.
From the very beginning...
For all these 26 years.
(CEO Park Jin Seok)
(My wife, Ko Seong Hui)
Yes?
Honey, it's me. I'm getting ahead of myself.
I'm so excited right now. I should have texted you first.
It's fine. I can talk. What is it?
I was just calling to make sure you don't have plans tonight.
Since our Yeong Ra is finally free, we need to throw a party for her.
Come straight home after work.
Okay. I will.
(Ji Eun Oh: Personal Information)
(Remarks)
(Current: Design Lead, AP Group)
About Lee Su Bin...
Remember the file you compiled without the director's knowledge?
Get me that file again.
(Lee Su Bin: Personal Information)
(Lee Ji Hyuk, older brother, Current CEO of AP Group)
The CEO of AP Group?
Su Bin graduated from a good university,
and she has a career she loves.
Her father worked at Gyeongseong T and C...
until his retirement,
and my friend, Ji Hyuk, is the CEO of AP Group.
Right, Seong Jae said his friend, Ji Hyuk,
was the CEO of AP Group.
But then... Ji Eun Oh?
She's the design team lead at AP Group?
So that's why she made me summon Lee Su Bin.
You know, that girl Seong Jae is seeing.
I looked into her, and her family's a total disaster.
Her dad's jobless. Her mom's a clerk,
and her brothers are no better.
And she's a YouTuber.
Her oldest brother is the CEO of AP, but she didn't mention it?
I thought you'd need to step in, but...
I guess that's not necessary anymore.
If you're worried about his future,
you can deal with it yourself.
So, CEO Lee Ji Hyuk...
knows about your relationship with Ji Eun Oh.
Is that why you tried to keep Lee Su Bin, Ji Hyuk's sister,
away from Seong Jae?
So that's it?
(Vice President Park Seong Jae)
Is she going to keep calling until I pick up or what?
What is it?
Hello, Seong Jae. Why so cold?
You made your choice. You don't get to be unhappy.
- Am I to manage your feelings? - No, your own.
That'll be all.
You told me not to get caught, so shouldn't you be helping me?
Hey, to celebrate Yeong Ra's stalker getting arrested today,
we're having a celebration dinner. Come straight home after work.
This is about your sister, Yeong Ra.
Is Father coming too?
Of course.
He was the first person I asked.
Okay, I'll be there.
(Vice President Park Seong Jae)
She wants us to have dinner, now of all times?
What on earth is she thinking?
(Mom)
It's my mom.
- Hello, Mom. - Yeong Ra, be home by 6:30pm.
We're all having dinner tonight to celebrate Yang Ji Il's arrest.
Is Seong Jae coming, too?
Of course, he is.
Don't be late.
Okay.
My mom sure is excited.
So Seong Jae must've promised he wouldn't tell Dad.
Why?
She wants me back by 6:30pm to celebrate Yang Ji Il's arrest.
But I just had ramyeon.
She doesn't know where Woo Jin is after he escaped from the hospital,
and she is throwing a party?
It just means she's confident she'll find him.
Her son ran away from her. How can she feel like celebrating?
Hey.
Are you still trying to make sense of my mom?
I haven't made this cake in a while.
This is your favorite, isn't it, Yeong Ra?
- Yes. - I like this one, too.
Please. You prefer tiramisu.
Go on, Yeong Ra. Blow them out.
Congratulations, sweetie!
Now, you're free!
You've been through so much, Yeong Ra.
Congratulations.
Shall we eat, everyone? You must be hungry.
Dad, you're staring at Mom again.
Dad, even after all this time, when you look at Mom...
Are you still so in love with her?
There's no one else like your mother.
I wonder if there's anyone else like her in the world.
That's why I'm so utterly devoted to you.
See, Seong Jae? Pleasing a woman is quite simple.
When a woman feels appreciated by her man,
she'll want to repay him ten times over.
She's right about that.
It's so touching, you almost want to be fooled by it.
What's Dad thinking?
Hey, Yeong Ra.
You should start getting out more and enjoy your freedom.
Okay.
Seong Jae's right, Yeong Ra.
And this year is off to such a great start.
We don't need Mr. Lee anymore, and Yeong Ra can go out on her own.
Our little girl is all grown up now.
So, Yeong Ra, what's happening with Mr. Lee?
There are still a few things to do, so he's working until tomorrow.
But I was so scared out of my mind.
I think I was way too overprotective of Yeong Ra.
But what could I do? That guy was no ordinary creep.
- Right? - You're absolutely right, but...
it's time you paid some attention to Woo Jin.
- Woo Jin? - Yes. Lately, you haven't...
mentioned his name once.
You're playing favorites, aren't you?
Honestly...
Come on. With Woo Jin, yesterday was the same as always,
and tomorrow will be the same. It's always study and exercise.
Yes, it's a 24-hour EKG monitoring device.
You'll just need to keep it on.
- Okay. - I'll be back to check on you.
How on earth did I end up here?
This is why everyone wants to be successful.
A three-day business trip to Tokyo.
Wow, that's really impressive.
A sudden trip like that could be a cause for concern.
Come on. I told you Ji Hyuk sounded cheerful.
Can you please stop being such a worrywart?
Anyway, it's his first trip abroad since he became the CEO.
I bet he'll bring us back presents.
What are you talking about, gifts? He'll be too busy for that.
Su Bin.
Is there anything you want your big brother to bring you?
No, not really.
Did you really have that little faith in me?
What?
I thought you seemed so gloomy and distracted lately,
but today, the old Ko Seong Hui is finally back.
I told you the arrest was a sure thing, didn't I?
I was that obvious, wasn't I?
But how could I not worry?
"What if he just gets probation? Yeong Ra's life would be ruined."
I was on pins and needles.
I know.
Okay. Next topic.
That girl Seong Jae was dating, Lee Su Bin.
What do her older brothers do for a living?
That's all in the past. Why are you asking about that now?
Because Seong Jae still seems so down about it.
So you're worried about him.
All right, fine.
It was his first romance in a while. Of course, he got swept up in it.
I guess I'll have to start looking for a good match for him again.
It's not like you to dodge a question.
Her brothers.
Goodness. They were nobodies. I barely remember.
It was some kind of rinky-dink company.
My friend, Ji Hyuk, is the CEO of AP Group.
So that's the real reason you were so against them dating.
Useless brothers are a worse red flag...
than an unemployed father.
I see.
My curiosity is killing me. I have to find out.
According to your MRI results,
we found signs that you've had viral myocarditis in the past.
You said you had a cold and aches a few months ago, right?
It was likely myocarditis then, but it went undiagnosed,
and it appears your heart has been gradually enlarging since then.
I see.
I didn't get an MRI.
I just thought it was a bad cold.
Should I put you on the transplant waiting list?
If I get on the transplant list,
how long would the wait be?
I can't say for sure right now.
As you may know, a heart can't come from any donor.
A registered organ donor has to become brain-dead,
and the waiting list is very long.
So...
if my turn never comes,
I'll just die waiting for a heart transplant.
Well, let's see.
Why the sudden trip to Tokyo? You said nothing about it at lunch.
I'm dying to know, so please tell me.
Ji Eun Oh...
(Ji Eun Oh)
And then, there's you.
- I'm home. - You're back?
Hey, Mom. Come here for a second.
What is it?
I told you not to hand-wash laundry. Your wrists are bad from the trays.
That's why your wrists are in such bad shape.
That's why I keep telling you to buy her a spin dryer.
Here you go.
What?
You need to take care of your wrists so they don't get any worse.
What's all this? Oh, my goodness.
Thank you, sweetheart.
- I'll take one right now, okay? - Okay.
My, this makes me so happy.
I bet they'll feel better in no time.
Hey, what about me? I carry trays, too.
Oh, please. You can just have some milk.
By the way, Gang Oh.
How was your meeting with the head office?
They rolled out the red carpet.
Now, I just have to look for a location.
Oh, you're carrying yourself differently...
now that you're the boss.
- Look at you, all on the ball. - You know it.
I've learned that an owner's mindset is what's really important.
Why did he suddenly go on a business trip?
I'm sure it's for company business.
(CEO Lee Ji Hyuk, Why the sudden trip to Tokyo?)
(I'm dying to know, so please tell me.)
What's gotten into him?
- What? - What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
This just isn't like him at all.
He says he likes me so much, so how could he not text back?
Did something happen at work?
Or what if he got into an accident?
Who got into an accident?
You scared me!
Ji Gang Oh, you should learn to knock.
Who got into an accident?
You were mumbling and couldn't hear me.
No, it's...
Oh, it's about Su Jeong.
Gang Oh, there's this guy who likes Su Jeong.
And she texted him.
But she says he hasn't replied.
How long has it been?
- Three hours? - Gosh, then he's not that into her.
No, he really does like her.
How would you know?
He's probably told her more than a dozen times.
That he really likes her. That he can't give up on her.
Women, seriously... Talk is cheap, right?
If he likes her that much, why no reply for three hours?
Goodness.
So, did he read the text or not?
He read it. I mean, she said he read it.
He's just stringing her along. He's definitely not into her.
Is Su Jeong a fool? How old is she? Why is she even asking this?
What would a little snot-nosed kid like you know?
Get out!
Wait, is this really about Su Jeong?
Hey! I said, get out.
But...
Of all people, why me?
What did I do to deserve this?
Life was just starting to get good.
It was finally worth living!
There's still so much I haven't done...
This is usually how it goes in the dramas.
Father, Mother.
I have no intention of ever getting married.
Why? Are you one of those types, too?
I hear that's the trend with young people these days.
Life's hard, so they give up on things one by one, even marriage.
It's not giving up. For some, it's a choice.
- I was the pathetic one, - For my generation...
blaming my parents and the world,
while going through life thinking I was all that.
- Ji Hyuk. - Then I made the worst choice ever.
Jung Bo A isn't coming.
I didn't want to live like this.
I didn't want to go on living like this.
And I truly wanted to start living right.
Do you think I don't know how much you resent, despise,
and belittle me?
But I still came here.
Because I needed to survive.
I struggled and clawed my way back.
I never apologized for making you give up your plans to study abroad.
For not keeping my promise,
I'm sorry.
Dad.
I was wrong.
I even reconciled with my father.
Thanks for trusting me.
I learned I find business most fulfilling.
And I achieved that.
I've liked you for a long time, and I've waited for you.
I never even stopped to consider your feelings.
I can't do this. I just can't do this anymore.
I can't, because I like you too much.
I...
I can't let you go.
I really think that until the day I die,
it is only ever going to be you.
How can I ever earn your forgiveness?
I fell in love with you.
And I really wanted to be with you.
(Why the sudden trip to Tokyo? You said nothing about it at lunch.)
Eun Oh...
She's finally curious about me.
(I'm dying to know, so please tell me.)
I even made up with my dad.
My work at AP is so much fun.
Everything is just perfect.
Does this mean it's my time to go?
It's telling me it's time to go.
It's his first business trip since becoming CEO.
It makes my heart pound, honey.
My heart's pounding too, but with worry.
Being notified of a work trip on the same day is highly unusual.
But I told you, his voice sounded fine.
- Should I give him a call? - Just leave him be.
And you need to stop worrying so much about Ji Hyuk.
All that kid thinks about is Eun Oh.
Then do you think he called that girl...
to say he arrived safely in Tokyo?
They're not officially dating yet.
They probably just exchanged a quick text or something.
- Have a good day, honey. - Thanks.
What are you up to today?
I'm organizing the budget proposal for the new scholarship recipients.
And I'm also getting a massage.
I thought your massage wasn't today.
I'm getting an extra one this week. Winter's making my skin dry,
and I just feel sluggish.
Good, you should.
Make sure you get the full treatment.
He's the kind of person who just agrees to anything.
Woo Jin, what excuse could I possibly have for letting you go?
Hey, Attorney Choi. I need to get some legal advice.
It's rather urgent.
Yes, it's something we should talk about in person.
I need you to make time before you leave work.
Did you find out the date of Woo Jin's outpatient appointment?
In ten days?
She's going to change the appointment.
Just let me get in touch with Woo Jin.
You think I won't go...
to Dongwoo Hospital in Busan with no number?
You can go, but you won't be able to see him.
I've already made all the arrangements.
Put more men on it tomorrow. And watch for appointment changes.
Why do you think ten is enough, Ms. Shin?
Double the men at every entrance to that hospital.
Why can't she just get it the first time?
You can go, but you won't be able to see him.
I've already made all the arrangements.
First, she could change the appointment date.
Second, she'll post bodyguards.
What else could there be?
What makes you so smugly confident?
The reason you transferred hospitals within Korea, Woo Jin,
is that you cannot fly for three months after your surgery.
I'll have to look into booking flights, then.
What on earth are you going to do?
Why are you asking? You said you'd quit.
Mind your own business and just hand in your resignation.
How can I possibly resign in a situation like this?
- "A situation like this?" - You want to forgive her, right?
Then forgive her. But if you do, just tell us.
Have you considered your children who have to watch, knowing it all?
Now is not the time.
No one's going to blame you for staying with her, Dad.
Why do you sound like you're giving me permission?
I just need to know for sure.
So I can decide whether to resign or not.
So you can't bring yourself to leave because you worry about your dad?
(CEO Lee Ji Hyuk)
He still hasn't texted me back. Don't you think that's a bit much?
You're right. That is weird. He always texts back immediately.
Or maybe he's just swamped with work?
No, if he were busy, he could just text, "Sorry, busy."
Is he really too busy to send two words?
You've got a point.
He's making me worry.
You've really got Ji Hyuk on your mind.
What? No...
How could I not worry when he's acting so weird?
It feels like he's blowing me off.
If he ignores this one too, I'm seriously done.
If you don't answer this time, I'm going to be really mad.
What do you want from me, Ji Hyuk? Is it that hard to text back?
Yes, it is, Eun Oh.
It's just too hard.
"Why are you rushing me?"
Su Jeong.
Is this really Ji Hyuk?
This is ridiculous. Why are you rushing me?
- I'm busy. - I know. That's so unlike Ji Hyuk.
Maybe someone's with him and messing with you?
What are you talking about? He's on a business trip alone.
No, this is totally his way of talking.
(Power off)
Eun Oh.
I have a very serious heart condition.
They say I need a heart transplant.
Mom, Dad.
They say I have to get a heart transplant.
My heart has become enlarged,
and they say it's not functioning properly.
This is...
a succession memorandum to restore your status as contracted author.
Mr. Lee Ji Wan, do you acknowledge Ms. Park is the author, Freedom?
Yes.
Bye.
Congratulations, Author Freedom.
Ji Wan, hearing someone other than you...
call me "Author Freedom" made me feel so weird.
You'll get used to it.
Now that I've signed the contract, I should get right to work.
Right.
You get to work. I have plans with some friends,
so I'll be out for an hour or two.
What?
You're leaving now?
Fine. I have to work anyway.
See you later.
What is this?
Who makes plans on our last day together?
Shouldn't he be having a farewell party with me?
He just ditches me now that I don't need his protection.
Now that I'm drawing them, the characters look a lot like us.
That's silly. A long-haired woman and a bodyguard-type guy...
are a pretty common trope.
After today, I really won't see him again.
But what's taking him so long to get back?
Yeong Ra! Hey, Yeong Ra!
- Come on out for one second! - Okay.
- Hurry up and come out! - Okay, I'm coming!
Surprise!
(Congratulations on the contract, Author Freedom!)
Ji Wan, what is all this?
Park Yeong Ra, congratulations...
on your first contract signed on your own.
Quick, blow out the candles.
Today's the day you officially became an author.
I couldn't go without throwing you a party to celebrate.
This is so beautiful.
So this is why you went out earlier?
Tiptoeing to hide all this from you, I nearly got a cramp in my calf.
I'm so touched.
And it's our farewell party, too.
I guess it is.
You must be cold. I'll get you a coat.
(Congratulations on the contract, Author Freedom!)
Here's to the debut of Author Freedom.
Here's to your last day at work...
Is that something to celebrate?
You really worked so hard, Ji Wan.
I do have one regret, though.
I never got to teach you self-defense.
I should have,
so you could go out in the world on your own, worry-free.
Without being afraid.
I'm not scared anymore. You've seen it yourself.
I know how to track locations now,
and I can even disguise myself to go undercover.
You're right. You used to be terrified of every little thing.
You've changed so much.
I thought you were really weird at first.
Right away, you were like, "How old are you?"
How old? I'm asking how old you are.
I'll have to ask my mom and get back to you on that.
You have to ask your mom just to tell me your own age?
Man, I was thinking, "Wow, I've never met such a brat."
That's not really a question for you to be asking.
There are exceptions and special cases in this world.
That was back when I was living under my mom's thumb.
Right.
The world you lived in seemed so completely different.
You seemed a little clueless.
I've changed a lot, thanks to you.
That's not it.
You were always like that. You just didn't realize it.
And what kind of person is that?
You're passionate about the things you love.
You're deeply caring and know how to appreciate others.
And you have a bold side to you, too...
That's the kind of person you are.
I just thought I had become prickly,
but I guess I had that side to me all along.
Thanks for helping me discover a part of myself I never knew.
It's nothing. I just figured it out while I was your bodyguard.
(Congratulations on the contract, Author Freedom!)
Ji Wan.
So, what are we now?
What do you mean, "What are we?"
What kind of question is that?
We're friends now, right?
At first, you were Seong Jae's friend's little brother.
Then a bodyguard and...
The young lady?
And after that...
We broke some rules together and tailed my mom.
And you even helped me brainstorm my webtoon's plot.
So, we're friends now, right?
Of course.
After all we've been through? Of course, we're friends.
No, actually.
We're comrades-in-arms.
Aren't you taking that with you?
It's a gift.
When you feel stuck on your webtoon, come out and have some coffee.
Once the weather warms up.
Thank you.
You should get going.
I will, once my designated driver gets here.
I need to see you get inside safely first.
Your shift is over.
Just for today, you go first.
I can handle this myself.
Still... You've been drinking, though.
I guess I can hold my liquor. I'm not even tipsy.
I'm serious.
I want to be the one to see you off.
All right. I'll head out first.
When will I see you again?
I'm sure we'll see each other around.
If we're friends, then I can call you whenever, right?
I should get going.
Why didn't he answer me?
I guess he doesn't want to keep in touch.
Fine, then.
Don't look back.
I'm not looking back. Do not look back, Lee Ji Wan.
If you look back now, you're a fool.
Friends? Yes, right. It's over.
Besides, Seong Jae and Su Bin were mixed up in this, too.
Take care, Yeong Ra.
She'll be fine.
But why does she keep weighing on my mind?
Your stats are stable, so you can be discharged.
But you can't overdo it.
Doctor.
In the next month or two,
the chances of a heart transplant becoming available for me...
are slim, right?
That's not something I can predict. However,
you have to stay hopeful.
Mr. Lee is coming straight to the office after landing.
Welcome back, Mr. Lee.
- Welcome back, Mr. Lee. - Yes. Has everyone been doing well?
Mr. Lee, did you have a good trip?
Cheol Min, can you get me that thing?
Yes, sir.
Oh, right.
About the job for my father... We've decided to call it off.
Oh, really?
I'm in for it now.
Cheol Min, what about that thing I asked for?
- Thanks. - Of course, sir.
All right.
Yes? What is it?
Did I do something wrong that day?
What day are you talking about?
The day you left for your trip.
The day before yesterday. When we had lunch together.
I have no memory of that.
Then why are you being like this to me?
The text I sent... Did you have to reply like that?
Send me the final Image House files. I need to take care of that today.
Gosh, I have so much to get through today.
So, can you send me those files right away?
Why is he being so cold?
Did I really do something wrong?
If he likes her that much, why no reply for three hours?
Gosh, then he's not that into her.
Don't tell me...
Don't tell me he got tired of me in just three days.
Mom, Dad.
My tastes have changed.
I don't like salty food anymore.
I do not care for soups or stews either.
At work,
something has come up that requires my full attention.
But that...
Why would I have to tell you that?
When you're the CEO,
you're bound to have secrets.
I'd prefer we keep things strictly business.
Ms. Ji Eun Oh.
This looks delicious.
I was rushed, so I grabbed these at the duty-free.
These are delicious.
Hey, what about the gift I asked for?
You asked him for a gift?
He was on a last-minute trip, and you asked him for a present?
Dad, it's okay. Don't be hard on him.
I just didn't have the time to get it.
You could've tried to make some time, though.
Hey, kids, you all keep eating.
My daughter's been feeling a little down,
my wife's worked so hard her wrist hurts,
my eldest son's tired from his trip, and Ji Wan has had a long day.
- So I'll do the dishes tonight. - Dad, come on. That's not fair.
It's fine. Just enjoy your snacks and tangerines.
Dad, don't worry. I'll do them.
Why would the guy who just got back from a three-day trip do the dishes?
Go get some rest. Go on.
Dad, about that whole Disaster Prevention Room scam...
"Scam?"
Well, since I tried to pull strings to get you in,
it was basically a scam.
About that, you were right, Dad.
He'll be taking over for me.
Everyone, please greet Chief Director Oh Jae Jin.
Right. He's actually my only son.
Out of greed, I had him start as an intern...
and work his way up to learn the ropes.
Please be understanding.
I'm Oh Jae Jin.
I had forgotten how that made me feel.
It wasn't fair, no matter how you look at it.
That's right. Yes, you were in the wrong for that.
And...
I got a job.
What?
I said, I got a job.
I got a call from the disaster control room...
of a mixed-use building.
For real?
Gosh, I should have just waited a few more days.
That's what I'm saying, kid. I told you I'd handle it myself,
so why did you have to go groveling to other people?
Parents and children should each do their best in their lives, son.
Hey, Mom!
Come on, if Dad got a job, you should've told me right away!
- What did you say? - Really?
Awesome!
My gosh!
Honey, you got a job?
Yes, I did.
Dad, why didn't you tell us?
I was going to tell everyone at once when the whole family was here.
I don't think so.
You wanted to brag to your eldest son, didn't you?
Come on, I wanted to be the one to tell him.
If I told anyone else in the family, word would've gotten out right away.
When did you hear from them?
Right when Ji Hyuk was leaving for his trip.
Are you kidding me? How did you keep it in for three days?
It's not that big of a deal.
What do you mean it's not a big deal?
You finally got a job as an electrical technician. Right?
It is a huge deal. Congratulations, Dad.
- You really pulled it off. - Congratulations, Dad!
Hey, my hands are all wet. Go on, get away.
Have Ji Wan do the dishes, Dad.
Oh, Yes? Buying me a celebration drink?
Well, that's... I'm sorry.
I was in meetings all night in Tokyo.
What was I thinking? You're tired. Go on, get some rest. Yes, go.
Okay.
Gosh, our family now has no worries. Nothing at all.
Don't you wish every day was like today?
- Yes. It's nice to finally relax. - Right?
Mom, I'm still unemployed, you know?
You have the security firm interview.
You'll get in, no problem.
- You'd better ace it this time. - Mind your own business.
- Don't come home unless you get in. - Why don't you move out?
This is nice.
I've got a great family.
(All voice recordings)
Just leaving work? Why were you at the office so late?
Because I didn't want to go home.
You should meet up with someone and vent.
Do you want me to come over?
But we broke up.
Eun Oh is still recovering,
so I can't ask her to go for a drink.
And since Ji Hyuk is your brother,
I can't ask him out for a drink either.
Seong Jae, you're really in a tough spot.
(The Brisket Master, Main Branch)
Their stir-fried brisket is incredible.
I love this spot. I didn't realize it was near your office.
Su Bin?
- Su Bin. - Is this guy nuts?
Hey, are you okay?
Hey! Stop right there! Did you just shove my Seong Jae?
Su Bin.
My gosh...
What is all this?
Honey, don't you need to take these documents?
(DNA test results, Ji Eun Oh and Ko Seong Hui)
Get out of this house before I get home from work.
Honey.
Please, just listen to me.
If you're still here when I get home,
just imagine what will happen. I left the documents there for you.
(DNA test results, Ji Eun Oh and Ko Seong Hui)
(Family Relation Certificate)
Even about Woo Jin...
(Han Woo Jin, Application for withdrawal)
Woo Jin dropped out of school?
(Han Woo Jin, Withdrawal Certification Letter)
From start to finish,
he's found out everything.
Park Jin Seok, you jerk.
How did he find out?
How could he have found out?
Right, no problems so far?
Are you sure the first step is complete?
Then prepare for the next step.
Mother.
So you're Eun Oh's birth mother?
Woo Jin had a liver transplant?
I found you out, and Woo Jin found you out.
And it looks like Yeong Ra has caught on, too.
Just make absolutely sure Dad never finds out.
After saying that, he snitched to his dad?
But he was acting totally normal up until yesterday.
No.
He must have known for a few days.
Then why blindside me today and tell me to get out?
Does he want a divorce, or does he want me to beg?
Of course, I did. You know me better than that.
The people I hate most are cheaters. Liars.
Woo Jin's on winter break, isn't he? You talk to him often, don't you?
"Often?" You know how sons are.
I think I spoke with him this past Monday.
He knew Woo Jin took a leave of absence...
and that he dropped out, but he still asked.
And I walked right into his trap.
Why would he wait this long to spring it on me?
So that's it.
Park Jin Seok, you've always had a ruthless side.
That's why I was always so careful.
It was like walking on thin ice.
I poured my blood, sweat, and tears to make that thin ice solid.
But even if I beg,
there's no guarantee he'll back down.
Then so be it.
(Vice President)
I'll handle this. Just turn a blind eye and stay out.
You know what Dad is like, don't you?
He'll never get over it. He chose to love Mom from the start.
Just let them live their own lives.
(Resignation Letter)
(Vice President Park Seong Jae)
Seong Jae.
Hey. Let's hang out.
Hey, I'm a CEO now. You can't just show up unannounced.
Let's go run a marathon. Here, put this on.
Hey.
Hold on.
What do you mean, a marathon? I haven't exercised in ages.
Right. Then let's go play some basketball.
Park Seong Jae, what's with you? This isn't like you.
I just feel so...
suffocated, that's why.
Oh, yes.
Hey, let's go for a bike ride then.
You said a hard ride clears the head and that it's exhilarating, right?
Why does it have to be exercise?
It's too cold. I don't want to.
I can't today.
Can't you tell I'm busy? I'm here working on a Saturday.
Then don't work today.
- Why shouldn't I? - Why do you say no to everything?
Hey, have I ever pestered you to do this or that with me?
Have I ever been this clingy with you before?
I feel so suffocated I think I'm going to lose my mind.
I miss Su Bin so much.
I want to call her. I want to go see her.
That alone is driving me crazy,
but on top of that, my family's a complete mess.
Hey, I have no room to breathe.
I can imagine.
Exactly.
So you need to take some responsibility too, man.
You were so against it. Have you no shame?
Shouldn't you be the one helping me get through this?
- I know. - Then why won't you?
It's not that I won't. I just can't.
Come on, no matter how busy you are, you can't spare me a few hours?
I can't exercise.
Why not?
Hey.
Hey, are you...
Are you crying?
Darn it.
Hey.
In a few days...
Fine.
Seong Jae,
I was going to tell you anyway.
You're going to have to clean up after me.
What are you talking about?
I need you to...
help me die with dignity.
Always leave an escape route, even when you're cornering a rat.
Does he really think I'll just get on my knees and beg?
(Files on Ji Eun Oh)
(Hyeonyu Department Store, Cheongju Orphanage)
(Our Golden Days)
I realize now that I completely misunderstood you.
- What if I told you I like you? - But I'm only telling you.
Heart transplant waiting list... Why were you looking that up?
You think we can be friends again, like nothing happened?
- Showing up here like this... - What do you want?
Didn't I tell you not to show me that face...
- when I walk in? - Let go!
Mom, what are you going to do?
Darn it... Is that jerk crazy? Hey! Park Yeong Ra!
Park Jin Seok!
You're a lot more dangerous than I thought.